

Husni Mubarak
Ailatat
Frontend Developer

#### How to reach me:

#### Cell:

082134510421

#### Email:

husniailatat@gmail.com

#### Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/husni-mubarak-ailatat-7186a2114/

#### Portfolio:

https://husnimubaraq.github.io/ portfolio/

### Address:

Bangunjiwo, Kasihan, Bantul, Yogyakarta

### **Personal Profile**

I am a Frontend Developer with more than 4 years experience. Have the ability and experience in designing, developing, and testing websites and mobile apps with the latest technology. Have experience using the programming language Javascript, PHP, C#

### **Education**

## **Universitas PGRI Yogyakarta**

S1 Teknik Informatika

## **My Skills**

- Javascript
- Typescript
- React / Next JS
- React Native
- Node JS / Express
- PHP
- Laravel
- Codeginiter
- · ASP.Net Core

### **Work Experience**

### **Frontend Engineer**

# Gramedusa Maret 2022 to present

- Building and developing websites and mobile apps
- Optimizing performance apps
- Collaborate with UI/UX on feature design and implementation

# **Frontend Developer**

PT Grahatour Maret 2020 to Februari 2022

- Building and developing websites and mobile apps
- Optimizing performance apps
- Collaborate with UI/UX on feature design and implementation

## **Frontend Developer**

PT Ramcou Buana Informatika Juli 2018 to Desember 2019

- Modify an existing website and mobile to upgrade the interface tested and refined software prior to rollout
- Building and developing android apps
- Provide time estimates to the tech lead or project manager and help identify tasks for developing the project plan as needed